<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
  <name>[O21] Thaumrim (Continued)</name>
  <packageId>Mlie.O21Thaumrim</packageId>
  <author>Neronix17</author>
  <url>https://github.com/emipa606/O21Thaumrim</url>
  <supportedVersions>
    <li>1.0</li>
    <li>1.1</li>
    <li>1.2</li>
  </supportedVersions>
  <modDependencies />
  <loadAfter />
  <description>[img]https://i.imgur.com/WAEzk68.png[/img]
Update of Neronix17s mod
https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=1567775191

- The robes and hood will now be considered cultist-clothing if using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2249174783]Call of Cthulhu - Cults[/url]
- Removed dependencies since the mod never got content that required them

[img]https://i.imgur.com/7Gzt3Rg.png[/img]

[table]
    [tr]
        [td][url=https://invite.gg/Mlie][img]https://i.imgur.com/zdzzBrc.png[/img][/url][/td]
        [td][url=https://github.com/emipa606/O21Thaumrim][img]https://i.imgur.com/kTkpTOE.png[/img][/url][/td]
    [/tr]
[/table]
	
[img]https://i.imgur.com/NOW7jU1.png[/img]
[b]Plans have been cut for this. I'm cutting back on a lot of plans in terms of Rimworld mods and this is one of the ones I've decided to cut. Sorry to those who've been waiting for the updates.[/b]

Thaumcraft (a veteran Minecraft mod by Azanor) introduced to the Rimworld universe.

[b]Currently Includes:[/b]
[list][*]Crimson Cult Robes
[*]Crimson Knight Armour[/list]

[b]Future Plans:[/b]
[list][*]Crimson Cult Faction and equipment, including buildings
[*]Thaumaturgy, various spells and abilities to be researched and unlocked.
[*]Essentia system
[*]Vis system powering Thaumaturgical magics.
[*]Loads of apparel and items.
[*]Golems
[*]Enemies other than the Crimson Cult
[*]Events for said enemies and various other things.[/list]

[h1][b]1.0 Load Order (1.1 handles it automatically):[/b][/h1]
[list][*]Core 
[*]HugsLib
[*]JecsTools[/list]

[b]Credit:[/b]
[list][*]Neronix17 - As of latest version created everything in the mod not otherwise credited.
[*]Jecrell - Apparel Shader to allow textures on crafted items to not be tainted by the colouring of the materials used.
[*]Azanor - creator of Thaumcraft, the original mod for Minecraft this is based on.[/list]

[img]https://i.imgur.com/Rs6T6cr.png[/img]
[list]
[*] See if the the error persists if you just have this mod and its requirements active.
[*] If not, try adding your other mods until it happens again.
[*] Post your error-log using [url=https://steamcommunity.com/workshop/filedetails/?id=818773962]HugsLib[/url] and command Ctrl+F12
[*] For best support, please use the Discord-channel for error-reporting.
[*] Do not report errors by making a discussion-thread, I get no notification of that.
[*] If you have the solution for a problem, please post it to the GitHub repository.
[/list]
</description>
</ModMetaData>
